orbitum.com 2016-05-22

# Orbitum - Politique de confidentialité

1\. Personal User Information Obtained and Processed by the Right Holder 

  * 1.1. For the purpose of this Policy, "Personal User Information" means the information that the User provides about himself or herself upon registration (creating an account) or when using the Software, including the User's personal data. The information mandatory for using the Software is specifically marked. Other information is provided by the User at his or her option.

1.2. The User is hereby notified and agrees that upon enabling the Software function of automatic statistics sending, the following anonymous Statistical Information (without a reference to the User) is automatically transmitted to the Right Holder to improve the quality of services provided to the User:

\- Information about the general Software performance

\- Information about the websites visited by the User — URL addresses

\- Information about the search queries made by the User through search systems and about following the advertisement links

\- Information about the contents of web pages viewed by the User, in this case the Software collects only information that may be identified as an offer of goods and services

Statistical information does not contain any data enabling User identification and/or data that may be treated as personal data.

The Right Holder may at its discretion change and/or supplement the types of Statistical Information without violating the guarantees laid down herein.

1.3. The User is hereby notified and agrees that when using the Software the following information will be automatically and anonymously (without a reference to the User) sent to the Right Holder: the type of the operation system installed on the User's device, the Software version and identifier, the statistics of used Software functions, and other technical information.

1.4. The User may at any time refuse to transfer the data listed in Clauses 1.1-1.3 hereof by disabling the respective functions.

1.5. This Policy is applicable only to the Software. The Right Holder does not control or bear any responsibility for third-party sites the User can go to by the links available in the Software, including in search results. Such sites may collect or request other personal data of the User, or perform other actions.

1.6. The Right Holder does not verify the validity of Personal Information provided by the Users or control their legal capacity. However, the Right Holder relies on the User to provide valid and sufficient Personal Information on the items in the registration form and to keep it updated. The consequences of providing wrong information are set out in the License Agreement -> <http://orbitum.com/terms>
